Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, records
1931-2009
RU 269
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
85.5
259.01
The records consist of the administrative files of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services at Yale University Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-B (YRG 32-B), Records of deputy, associate, and assistant university librarians of Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
The records are partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of the administrative files of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services at Yale University Library.
Academic libraries -- Administration; Public services (Libraries); Yale University -- Administration; Yale University. Library
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, 1972-1982; Accession 1984-A-065 (Box 1–5)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2017
  Scope and Contents
  No online inventory available. Paper inventory available in repository.
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, circa 1973-1986; Accession 1988-A-080 (Box 1, Box 1AD, Box 2, Box 2AD, Box 3, Box 3AD–5AD)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2021
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, circa 1977-1987; Accession 1988-A-086 (Box 1–4)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2022
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, circa 1974-1987; Accession 1988-A-097 (Box 1–6)
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, 1976-1986; Accession 1990-A-020 (Box 1)
- Records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, Yale University, circa 1983-1996; Accession 1996-A-077 (Box 1–9)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2035
- Records of the Library Management Council and associated subject files, 1997-1998; Accession 2003-A-086 (Box 1)
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2037
  No inventory available.
- Records of Danuta Nitecki as Associate University Lbrarian for Public Services concerning the Library Shelving Facility, 1996-2001; Accession 2003-A-121
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2036
  - Implementation/Committees (Box 1)
  - Collections, Processing, Services (Binder 1), 1997-1998 (Box 1)
  - Staffing, Coordination Groups, Action (Binder 2), 1997-1999 (Box 1)
  - Locator, Software, GFA (Binder 3), 1998 (Box 1)
  - Software (Binder 3A)
    - Generation Fifth Application, Inc (Box 2)
    - License Agreement (Box 2)
    - GFA/Follow-up to 8/13/1998 Teleconference (Box 2)
    - GFA Project Time Line (Box 2)
    - Info on scanner labeling products to go with Library Archival system software (Box 2)
    - License for Harvard Library archival system software (Box 2)
    - Harvard Depository -General Operations Description (Box 2)
    - Infotrak, 1998 (Box 2)
    - OCSF Locator Software Proposals -Review (7 copies) (Box 2)
    - Draft locator software review, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Vendor question (Box 2)
    - YUHS Pharmacy System Recommendation (Box 2)
  - Implementation -announcements, Public Forum, Background, Related PR, Public Comments, Assessment (Binder 4), 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Operations/Construction -Site Selection, Facility Construction, Planograph, Consultants (Binder 6), 1996-1998 (Box 2)
  - Operations/post-construction -Moving, Policies, Access, Other Users, Other Sites, Tours, Building Issues, Operations, Equipment, Supplies (Binder 7), 1997-2001 (Box 3)
  - Construction Meetings (Architects) (Binder 8) (Box 3)
  - 2ndModule (Binder 9), 2001 (Box 3)
  - Working Group for an Off-Campus High-Efficiency Shelving Facility (2), 1996 (Box 4)
  - Yale University Off-Campus Shelving Facility (Box 4)
  - First Floor Plan Bid Set, 1998 January 2 (Box 4)
  - Construction Set -Phase I, 1998 February 20 (Box 4)
  - Carpeting for LSF, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Phase 2, Permit Set, Volume 1, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Phase 2, Permit Set, Volume 2, 2001 (Box 4)
  - First Floor Plan (single sheet), 2001 (Box 4)
  - Phase 2 -complete set of floor plans, 2001 September (Box 4)
  - Phase 2 -Complete set of plans, 2001 (Box 4)
  - Yale University Library - Manuscripts & Archives Relocation Annex to LSF Project Proposal - Presented to Ms. Diane Brown, 1998 (Box 4)
  - The Virtual Document exchange Product Description (VDX) Fretwell-Downing, Inc., 2000 (Box 4)
  - Barr & Barr Builders, Inc. 1" grey/low- grey ann. air-poly/butyl, low-e ann. Surf #3 Alternate submittal - lord E coating on surface #3 - piece for glass from Solar Seal Company, 55 Bristol Drive, South Easton, Mass. 02375 (Box 5)
  - Yale off campus shelving facility, phase 2, architectural drawings, 2001 (Box 6)
- Records of Danuta Nitecki as Associate University Librarian for Public Services, including files from Library Development, circa 1980-2001; Accession 2004-A-100
  Arranged alphabetically by topic.
  - Alliance, 2001 (Box 1)
  - Annual Revisions -YUL Publications, 1998-2001 (Box 1)
  - Arts of the Book
    - Arts of the Book, 1999- 2000 (Box 1)
    - Digital Media Center, 1998 (Box 1)
  - Cash handling, 1997 (Box 1)
  - Circulation
    - Privileges, 2000- 2001 (Box 1)
  - Course Support
    - Background, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
    - Copyright Guidelines, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Faculty Participants & Assessment, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Phase 2, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Proposal & Meeting Notes, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
  - Culpepper Grant, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - Disabilities
    - Building access, 1996-1998 (Box 1)
  - Exhibits
    - Tercentennial, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
  - Facilities
    - Loans for Exhibits, 1999-2000 (Box 1)
    - Request for Use of YUL Facilities, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Support Program
    - Grant Evaluation, 1998-1999 (Box 1)
    - Grant Proposals (originals), 1998-1999 (Box 1)
  - ID Card, 2000 (Box 1)
  - Information Technology Service
    - Information Technology Services Advisory Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 1)
    - ITS Related Projects, 1997-1999 (Box 1)
    - ITSAC Infrastructure and Services Subcommittee, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
    - ITSAC Instruction Subcommittee (Box 1)
  - Instruction
    - Instruction: Hewlett Grant, 1996, 1997 (Box 1)
  - LMS Migration
    - Site Visit -Penn, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Site Visit Group (Box 1)
  - Laptops
    - Reader Network Access, 1996-1998 (Box 1)
  - Maps
  - Moore
  - NERC, 2000 (Box 1)
  - New Haven Affairs (Box 1)
  - Patron Queries
    - Suggestion Box (Box 1)
  - Ad Hoc Group on Use of Unstaffed Public Reading Rooms in SML and CCL, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
  - American Studies Reading Room, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Andrews Study, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Microform Reader -Printer, 1997, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Photocopy -COPICO, 1997, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Oral History -American Music, 1997, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Signage Issues, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Reference Services
    - General Reference Service Group, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Map Collection (Box 2)
  - SML: Stack Issues -Entrance, 1999 (Box 2)
  - SML: Access Services: Merge: Circ, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Wireless Access in SML-CC, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Access to ORBIS -SML Nave (Box 2)
  - Service Quality Planning Retreat, 2000 (Box 2)
  - SML Group (Good Neighbors Agenda and Notes, 2001) Agenda topics for Gotham, - 1997 (Box 2)
  - Sterling Memorial Library/Cross Campus Library CCL Extending Hours, 1997-2002 (Box 2)
  - Student Relations Calhoun College Project, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Teaching and Learning
    - Center for Teaching and Learning -, 1998 (Box 2)
    - Teaching and Learning Retreat -, 1997 (Box 2)
  - Travel, 1999-2001 (Box 2)
  - TrumbullCollegeFellows, 1997, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Visitors to the Library, 1998-2000 (Box 2)
  - WAG, 1999-2001 (Box 2)
  - Yul Web Presence
    - Alumni Access to Web-Based Materials, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Library Front Door, 1997 (Box 2)
  - CSVR Chron files
    - 1/1993-9/1994 (Box 3)
    - 10/1994-10/1995 (Box 3)
    - 10/1995-6/1996 (Box 3)
    - 6/1996-7/1996 (Box 3)
    - 1/1/1992 (Box 4)
    - 1/20/1989-1/26/1991 (Box 4)
    - 8/6/1996-6/30/1998 (Box 4)
    - 9/1987-9/1990 (Box 4)
    - 9/1986-98/1987 (Box 4)
    - 6/16/1987-1/4/1988 (Box 4)
    - 1/5/1988-7/31/1988 (Box 4)
    - 1/2/1986-6/15/1987 (Box 4)
    - 9/1985-8/1986 (Box 4)
    - 9/1984-8/1985 (Box 4)
    - 1/1980-7/1983 (Box 4)
  - Register of the records of the Librarian
    - Vol. 1 of 3 -series 0-2 (Box 5)
    - Vol. 2 of 3 -series 3 - 18 (Box 5)
    - Vol. 3 of 3 -series 19 - 32 (Box 5)
- Reader's exhibit records, Fall 2004; Accession 2005-A-081
  Open for research use.
  - Invitation (Box 1)
  - Ad "Readers Welcome to Campus" (Box 1)
  - Reading Exhibit Replies (Box 1)
  - Digital picture of sign and write-up (Box 1)
  - Reading encourages…….. (Box 1)
  - D. Nitecki introduction (Box 1)
  - Book Exhibit Participators (Box 1)
  - Readers Welcome to Campus Book List (Box 1)
  - Response to Book Selection (Box 1)
  - Russell Shaddox pictures of Reception (digital camera shots on paper) (Box 1)
  - Receipts of books borrowed from library (Box 1)
  - Pictures brought to Printko - Branford (Box 1)
  - CD rom pictures of Exhibitors obtained from Mike Marsland of Public Affairs (Box 1)
  - Digital pictures of exhibitors and write-ups (Box 1)
  - Cardboard signs of Readers Welcome..,Danuta's intro, large sign at Door (Box 1)
  - The following folders contain the following information: picture of exhibitor, mounting write-up, digital picture of book, exhibitor and write-up and a hard copy of the write-up
  - Exhibitors Folders (Box 1)
    - President Richard Levin (Box 1)
- Records of Danuta Nitecki as Associate University Librarian for Public Services, 1996-2002; Accession 2005-A-158
  - Binder 1 -COPY -Borrow Direct Pilot - RLG-PS Contracts, 1996 - 2001
    - RLG -CPS Contracts (Box 1)
    - Governing Agreements (Box 1)
    - Progress Report (Box 1)
    - RLG Project Management (Box 1)
    - Related Items (Box 1)
    - AUL Policy Group (Box 1)
  - Binder 2 -COPY -Phase II, 2001-2002
    - Government Issues (Box 1)
    - Server Consolidation (Box 1)
    - CIC (Box 1)
    - Alternative Options (Box 1)
    - Copy Assessment (Box 1)
    - ALA - COPY (Box 1)
  - Binder -CPS URSA User's Guide -Version 2, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Binder -CPS -URSA Product Specification -Version 2, 1997 (Box 1)
- Chronological files of Danuta Nitecki as AUL for Public Services, 1996-1999; Accession 2005-A-159
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2034
  - Danuta's Nitecki's Chron, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CSVR CHRON, 1993-1999 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Copy -YaleYUL System Issues, 1996- 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Publicity Yale (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Earlier Discussions (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Assorted records from the University Librarian's office maintained by the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, including budget proposals and the Library Shelving Facility, 1999; Accession 2005-A-164 (Box 1)
- Administrative records of Danuta Nitecki as Associate University Librarian for Public Services, circa 1997-1999; Accession 2006-A-090
  - Exhibits binder -instructions copy given to D. Timlin (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Yale University Budget, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - YaleUniversityBudget, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - SML Stack Maps -Final Version, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence of Danuta Nitecki as Associate University Librarian for Public Services, circa 1996-2004; Accession 2006-A-118
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2039
  - Correspondence
    - Document Delivery Process Improvement, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Shipping & Delivery Improvement Group, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Exhibits -Applications, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
    - Reading Exhibit - Miscellaneous, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Reading Exhibit -Reception/Publicity, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Reading Exhibit - Statements, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Exhibits -Web Pages, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Film Studies Center, 1998, 1999 (Box 1)
    - Forestry Library Review, 1999, 2000 (Box 1)
    - Instruction Proposals, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Instruction -Arts Library, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Instruction -Campus Resources, 1997, 1998, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Instruction: YCE Report, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Instruction Distance Learning -Ivy Plus, 1997 (Box 1)
    - Instruction Forum -Current Undergraduate support Activities, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Instruction -Handouts & PR, 1997, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Instructions -Yale College Education, 2002, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Instruction -Other Institutions - Samples, 1997, 1998 (Box 1)
    - Instruction -Sample Program, 1996, 2001 (Box 1)
    - ITS Policy, 2003 (Box 1)
    - ITS/Library Collaborative Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Library Course Support, 2003 (Box 1)
    - ITS Library Roundtable, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Library Hours, 1998-2001 (Box 1)
    - Library Hours, 2001-2002 (Box 1)
    - Library Hours, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Libraries for the Future, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Library -Space Alterations, 1999-2001 (Box 1)
    - Library -EASL Space Planning, 2001 (Box 1)
    - Library -Social Science Bldg (Box 1)
    - Permissions, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Permissions, 2002 (Box 1)
    - Permissions - Photographing, 2002-2003 (Box 1)
    - Permission for Reproduction, 2000-2001 (Box 1)
    - Permissions -Misdirected Applications to Publish Materials, 1998-2002 (Box 1)
    - Alliance for the Data Documentation Initiative (DDI) Univ of Mich, 2003-2004 (Box 2)
  - Architectural Archives, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Arts Library -Library Subgroup, Arts Library Project, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Arts - History of Art: Program, History and Space, 1997 (Box 2)
  - ArtsBuilding- VRC, 2001 (Box 2)
  - AUL Presentations, 1996-2003 (Box 2)
  - AUL -Sharing Information among AUL's, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Audio Visual Library Services - CCL, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Borrow Direct Assessment, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Borrow Direct, 2002-2003 (Box 2)
  - Pigasus Contract, 2001 (Box 2)
  - General Circulation Issues, 2000-2004 (Box 2)
  - Loan Privileges -Non-campus - Circulation Loan Rationale, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Circulation - Privileges -Patron Status, 2002-2003 (Box 2)
  - Circulation - Privileges -Policies General, 2000 (Box 2)
  - Circulation Privileges, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Club Quarters, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Colleges: Masters Council Collaborations, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Schedule & Task Lists, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Pigasus Contract, 2001 (Box 2)
  - Copy Workflow Group, 1997-1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy - Authentication, 1997-98 (Box 2)
  - Copy -URSA Demo, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Specs: Catalog, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Searching Chapter, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Non-Returnables, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Picklists and Filtering, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Recall, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Copy -Sorting, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Copy - Renewal, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Document Delivery -Desktop, 2003 (Box 2)
  - Collaborative Teaching & Learning Project, 2004 (Box 2)
  - Course Support, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Copyright Guidelines, 1999-2001 (Box 2)
  - Disability - Library Services for Persons w/ Disabilities, 1996 (Box 2)
  - Disability - Accessibility Resource Network, 2000-2001 (Box 2)
  - Direct Reports Budget, 2000-2003 (Box 2)
  - Direct Reports meeting, 2000-2002 (Box 2)
  - Misfiled Items -1994, 1995, 1993, 1991, 1985, Dev, Recommendations (Box 2)
  - Library Strategic Plan -Mgmt of Collection Planning Group, 2001-2003 (Box 2)
  - LMT Strategic Planning, 2002 (Box 2)
  - Library Strategic Plan -Mgmt Collection & User Expectation, 2001-2002 (Box 3)
  - Strategic Plan: Goal Groups, 2001-2002 (Box 3)
  - Business Case for Change -QI Acq., 2003 (Box 3)
  - Business Case for Change -QI Acq., 2003 (Box 3)
  - Administrative Quality Oversight group, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Implementation Architecture, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Improving Process to Acquire Library Materials, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Selection Acquisition Process Improvement -BCC Team, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Process Improvement -First Steps, 2000 (Box 3)
  - Quality Improvement -ELI Express, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Quality Improvement -Acquisitions (1), 2003-2004 (Box 3)
  - QI Select & Acq -Final, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Acquisitions Overview & Key Indicators, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Redesign Team for Selection/Acquisition, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Selection Acquisition Process Improvement - Steering, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Selection Acquisition Process Improvement -General Information, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Implementation Team -M. Bellinger, 2003 (Box 3)
  - SQI-Quality Time, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Libraries Update, 2003 (Box 3)
  - LSF -Visit Stanford & Brown, 2002 (Box 3)
  - LSF Ribbon Cutting, 2002 (Box 3)
  - LSF Publicity/Celebrations, 2002 (Box 3)
  - LSF Tour, 2004-2005 (Box 3)
  - LSF -Michael DiMassa, 2004 (Box 3)
  - LSF Transfers - Budget, 2004 (Box 3)
  - ILL, 2004 (Box 3)
  - Inter-Library Loan (ILL), 1997-2002 (Box 3)
  - Mudd, 1997-2001 (Box 3)
  - Mudd Access -Policy Issues, 1998-2003 (Box 3)
  - Mudd Library Budget changes, 1998-2000 (Box 3)
  - Computer printing -photocopying, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Public Relations, 2001-2004 (Box 3)
  - Publications, 2003 (Box 3)
  - Reference -Ask!Live, 2002 (Box 3)
  - Registration Form -ARL/OLMS Webcast Registration, 2004 (Box 3)
  - SQI, 1999 (Box 4)
  - SQI - Photographer, 2002 (Box 4)
  - SQIC Comments, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Service Quality Awards Ceremony, 2000-2001 (Box 4)
  - Awards Ceremony, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
  - Service Quality Awards, 2001 (Box 4)
  - SQIC Blurbs, 2002 (Box 4)
  - SQIC Update, 2003 (Box 4)
  - SQIC Ref, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Solving Water Mold, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
  - Shoah Mellon Grant, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Shoah -survey, plan, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Shoah Fd./Mtg Assessment, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Security -Lost Books - Hugnet, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Security -Law Firm Books, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Service Standards Group, 1995-1998 (Box 4)
  - SQIC Instruction Group Report, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Sterling Memorial Library - signs, 2003 (Box 4)
  - SML Entry Floor Map, circa 1996-2004 (Box 4)
  - CCl Extended Hours, 2004 (Box 4)
  - CCl Collections Committee, 2001-2003 (Box 4)
  - Food in Nave, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Food & Drink in YUL, 2001 (Box 4)
  - General Information Services, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Library Questions, 2004 (Box 4)
  - New Staff Reception, 2003 (Box 4)
  - New Staff Bio's, 2004 (Box 4)
  - Periodical Reading Room, 1997-2001 (Box 4)
  - Publicity, 2004 (Box 4)
  - English Graduate Reading Room, 2004 (Box 4)
  - CCL issues, 2003 (Box 4)
  - Stack Cleaning, 1997 (Box 4)
  - Stacks Measures, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Graduate Students -Circulation, 1998-1999 (Box 4)
  - Graduate Students: General Issues, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Committee on College Education, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Undergraduate Regulations, 1996-2003 (Box 4)
  - Undergraduate Students: General Issues, 2001 (Box 4)
  - CCL -Head Count, 1996 (Box 4)
  - SML Renovations, 2002 (Box 4)
  - Space -History Read. Rm map, circa 1996-2004 (Box 4)
  - Surveys (Box 5)
  - Directory of Special Libraries, 2003 (Box 5)
  - ACRL Survey, 2003 (Box 5)
  - NCES, 2002 (Box 5)
  - Encyclopedies Quid, 2003 (Box 5)
  - Surveys -Borrow Direct & Staff Survey, 2001-2002 (Box 5)
  - Surveys - Miscellaneous, 2003, 2004 (Box 5)
  - SPEC Survey, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Teaching & Learning, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
  - Yale College -Committee on Teaching and Learning, 2003-2004 (Box 5)
  - Teaching & Learning, 2004 (Box 5)
  - CLIR Sponsors Symposium, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Visitors
    - French Librarian, 2003 (Box 5)
    - Swiss visitor, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Steve Hiller -SQIC Prog on Assessment, 2004 (Box 5)
  - Staff Front Door, 2003 (Box 5)
- Reports and memoranda concerning the Circulation Department and Binding Committee report, 1931-1968; Accession 2006-A-215
  - Report of the Binding Committee, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda regarding Circulation, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda regarding Circulation, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda regarding Shelving, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Administrative records of the Associate University Librarian for Public Services, 1997-2005 (inclusive); Accession 2007-A-040
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2040
  Arranged by topic.
  - Integration Planning, 1999 - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - D. Nitecki -Chronological File, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Service Subgroup for Disabilities, 1998 - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Advisory Committee -Disabilities, 1997-2002 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - MSSA -Gehry, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - ENCompass User Guide, circa 1997-2005 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - D. Nitecki -Chronological File, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Innovative Interfaces, circa 1997-2005 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Administrative records of Danuta Nitecki as associate university librarian for public services, 1996-2006; Accession 2007-A-158
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - Competencies for Public Services -CT Library Association, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Corporate Express, 2004-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Expense Reports, 1997-2006 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - EMS Bills, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - History of Art Group Assessment, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - History of Art Support Team, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - LSF Trips & Tours -Kodak pictures, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Phase 2 Renovations, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Phase 2A -Nave & Card Catalog, 2006 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Phase 2 Website -Established, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Summer '04 - Projects, 2004 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Knowledge Management, 2002-2004 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Think Tank -ITS Collaborative, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Web Advisory Group, 1996-1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Workstations (Public Research) Policy Change, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Assessment -Borrow Direct, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Assessment -CCL, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Assessment -Survey -Front Door, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - LMT -Capital Campaign, 2006-2010 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Reference Stats, 2005 October-2006 June (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Reference Stats, 2005 Ju-l2005 October (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Reference Sample Figures, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Reference Sample Figures, 2004-2005 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Reference Stats, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Reference Sampling -Holly, 2003-2004 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Reference Sampling, 2002-2003 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Shipping Memo, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Advisory Committee on Library Policy records, circa 1971-1994; Accession 2007-A-153
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2030
  - Minutes, memos, agendas, handouts and correspondence, 1971-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1 - 3)
- Records of Karin Trainer and Danuta Nitecki as Associate University Librarian for Public Services [computer files], 1992-2000; Accession 2007-A-191 (Box 1–5)
  Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
  - Stacks Directory & Floor Plans, 1998-2000; 170
    General note
    Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
  - Library Hours, 452
  - Statistics, 1994-2000; 355 computer files (XLS, DOC)
  - RCB KAT Backup, 1993-1996; 1541
- Cross Campus Library (now Bass Library) renovation records, 1995-2007; Accession 2008-A-133
  The materials are open for research.
  - Sterling Memorial Library Phase 1 Renovation Plans, 1995 (Box 1)
  - Bass Dedication, 2007 November (Box 2)
  - CCL Basement and Sub-basement plan, 2004 April (Box 2)
  - Re-arrangements and Improvements at the Sterling Memorial Library, 2005 August (Box 2)
  - CCL Prepares for Renovation, 2005 August (Box 2)
  - Collection Space Improvements at SML, 2005 August (Box 2)
  - Samples -CCL furniture, paneling rugs, 2006 (Box 3)
  - Opening photos-Bass Library, 2007 October 19; Shapiro, Harold; 327 computer files (JPEG)